饥饿
的青春
第二季  第十七集
0,0,0,fx,学习
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,进步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译   roaddogX1
翻译  roaddogX2
校对  roaddogX3
时间轴 JimmyBeck
后期 斯人       总监 全是roaddog
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
乔什
Hey Josh.
我俩都给你买了礼物
We each got you something
庆祝你新应用发布
to kick off the launch of your new app.
发布快乐
Appy-birthday!
你懂没  是发布日
Get it? App-y instead of happy?
是我想到的
I thought of it.
你们有谁送的是赞安诺吗
Do any of them happen to be a xanax?
我开玩笑而已  并没有
I'm just kidding. No, I'm not.
早上好
Good morning!
怎么了
What's... what's going on?
这是干什么
What's happening?
"干什么"吗
"What's happening?"
乔什今年发布的第一款新应用
The first new app Josh has released
还有半小时就要上线了
in a year is going live in 30 minutes.
为了让他在这能成就或者毁灭
And to distract him from this crucial moment
他事业的关键时刻别太紧张
that could make or break his career,
爱他的人们  送给了他礼物
The people that love him are giving him presents.
是啊  我知道是这事
Oh, yeah. I mean I know that's happening.
我是问还有其他事吗
I meant... you know, what's happening else?
没了
Nothing.
你要送他什么
What did you get him?
我...
I...
我要送...  不
I got him a-- oh no...
差点被你骗了
Ha ha, almost got me.
这是个惊喜
It's a surprise.
各位  你们不用送我东西的
Guys, you didn't have to get me anything.
很好  因为她显然没准备
Good, because she obviously didn't.
我准备了  实际上我的礼物很棒
Yes I did. In fact, my gift is so amazing,
还很私密  无法描述
And personal, and indescribable,
我就不描述了
I'm going to stop describing it.
拆我的  拆我的
Open mine! Open mine!
是最好的自行车架
It's a top of the line bike rack!
艾略特  你把我的两大爱好结合了
Elliot, you combined my two favorite things.
自行车和巨乳[架子]  击个掌
Bikes and racks. Up top!
我得承认  艾略特  我之前还怕
Well, I have to admit, Elliot, I was afraid
你的礼物比我有心思
that your gift would be better.
但没有哦
But it's not!
这是什么
What is-- what is this?
摇头娃娃啊
It's a bobblehead.
你的娃娃  我定做的
Of you! I had it made.
我该...
Where...
把这娃娃放哪啊
am I gonna put this bobblehead?
我太喜欢了
I love it.
真讨厌我的礼物还不来
I'm so mad that my gift isn't here yet.
你就好拆开了
So you can open it-- oh!
让我来看看运单
Let me check on the tracking.
不好
Yeah... oh no.
在...暴风雪地区有场暴风雪
There's a stupid snowstorm in the... snowstormy areas.
快看
Oh look.
上面说傍晚就能到了...吧
It says it's going to be here by late afteroon-ish.
我能先去吃午餐吗
Unrelated, can I take an early lunch?
莉莉廉价服装店
这礼物一定要特别
Okay. This gift has to be unique,
私密  还要少于我们在沙发缝找到的十二块钱
And personal, and less than the $12 we found in the couch.
一顶软呢帽怎么样
How about a fedora?
别学菲董
Nah, too Pharrell-y.
好吧  那...
All right, so...
马甲如何
how about a vest?
太艾略特风了
Too Elliot-y.
好吧
Okie-dokie... ooh!
送高领衫
a turtleneck.
又不是演哑剧
Too mime-y.
是吗  史蒂夫·乔布斯演哑剧吗
Really? Was Steve Jobs a mime?
可能吧
Maybe.
但他不是搞电脑的大人物吗
But wasn't he like a big huge computer guy?
没错  这是他的标志性衣服
Yes, and this was his signature shirt!
黑色的高领套头衫
A black mock turtleneck.
你真觉得乔什那么书呆
You really think Josh is that much of a nerd
只因为史蒂夫·乔布斯穿这个
that he's gonna like a black mock turtleneck
就也会喜欢黑色高领衫吗
just because Steve Jobs wore one?
-也是  -不不不  这很完美
- He probably-- - No no no! It's perfect!
多少钱
How much is it?
十五块
Fifteen dollars.
该死  钱不够
Dammit. We don't have enough.
有我小索在  谁敢原价卖给你
Well, you don't need enough when you got Li'l So so.
八块钱  不卖就算
Ahem, eight bucks. Take it or leave it.
那算了
Leave it.
别嘛  姑娘
Come on, chica.
这破衣服哪里值十五块
This crappy old shirt isn't worth $15.
我们肯定有办法的
There's gotta be something we can do.
那就再加七块
Add $7.
七块
That's this many.
拜托  莉莉
Please, Lily!
廉价莉莉
Frugal Lily.
廉价莉莉小姐
Miss Frugal Lily.
这是送我老板的  如果我不送他礼物
This is for my boss, and if I don't get him something,
可能会丢工作
I could lose my job.
好吗  我闺蜜现在又没工作
Okay? And my best friend isn't working right now,
我是家里唯一挣钱的人了
so I'm the only one working in the family.
这样吧亲爱的  便宜三块
Tell you what sweetheart, three dollars off
留个信箱地址就好
if you join the mailing list.
没问题
Okay.
不用谢
You're welcome.
应用已经上线一小时了
Okay, the app's been live for an hour now.
下载量如何
How are the numbers?
按我首席财务总监的话是
I believe the way my Chief Financial Officer
"天啊  怎么会"
put it was, "Oh god! Oh god! Why?"
结束了  艾略特  失败了
It's over, Elliot. It failed.
我看得出来你不高兴
I can see you're upset.
你想让我...
Would you like me to...
下载啊
Come on!
闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
你才闭嘴
You shut up.
我快疯了
I'm losing it.
没错  是的
Yeah. Ya are.
你没了优势  没了天赋
Losing your edge. Losing you talent.
你在业内没地位了
You're not relevant anymore.
够了
Enough.
废物
Loser!
不
Nope.
这么大的东西塞不进那小洞啊
Not easy fitting something so big through such a small hole.
他说道
That's what he said.
我这么妙语连珠  居然边上没人听
I come up with a zinger like that and no one's around to hear it.
还以为有钱人的垃圾会香一点
You would think rich people's trash would smell better.
我猜所以他们有的才是"臭钱"吧
I guess that's why they call 'em stinkin' rich.
我要把这些段子写下来
Damn, I got to start writing this stuff down.
怎么回事
What the hell?
是我送给乔什的摇头娃娃
That's the bobblehead I got for Josh.
那没良心的混...
That ungrateful son of a--
还好我没送他小狗
good thing I didn't go with the puppy.
猜猜你有什么
Guess what you got?
一个烂透了的应用吗
An app that's going nowhere?
猜猜还有什么
Guess what else?
那个没人相信我买了的礼物
The gift arrived that no one believed I got you!
到了  快拆开看看
It's here! Open it, open it, open it...
黑色高领衫
Black turtleneck.
就是史蒂夫·乔布斯穿的那种
It's the same kind that Steve Jobs wore.
送你是因为你让我想起了他
I got it because you remind me of him.
我怎么就跟乔布斯一样了
How am I like Steve Jobs?
他那么成功
Steve Jobs was successful.
他也不是总成功的嘛
Well you know, he wasn't always.
他也起起伏伏的  是吗
He had-- he had ups and downs, right?
当然
Of course he did.
对  他有过成功  也有过失败
Yeah. You know, he had success and he had failure.
这跟你刚才说的是一个意思
I mean that's the same thing you just said,
但我懂了
but I see where you're going.
等等
Wait a minute.
你买这高领衫  是提醒我
You got me this turtleneck to remind me that
就算乔布斯多次失败过
even though Steve Jobs had some occasional disappointments,
结果还是称霸了整个科技界
he went on to take over the entire world of technology.
或许我也可以
And maybe I will too.
对  就像我贺卡上写的
Yeah. It's like you read my card.
我礼物选对了吗
So was I right about the gift?
很对  我送他的时机也刚刚好
Yes! And I gave it to him at the perfect time.
就在他应用失败的时候
Right when his app was failing.
不是吧  失败了吗
Oh no. His app is failing?
你想知道最棒的是什么吗
So you want to know the best part?
他很喜欢  那给了他希望
He loved it. It gave him hope.
送礼物不就是为了这个吗
And isn't that what gift giving is all about?
廉价服装店的莉莉
Lily! From Frugal Lily's!
记性真好  两小时前的人你还记得
Great memory, you met me two hours ago.
我想要回高领衫
I need the turtleneck back.
抱歉  莉莉  那衣服不卖
I'm sorry, Lily, the shirt's not for sale.
那就想办法卖
Well, make it for sale.
后来发现那衣服真是史蒂夫·乔布斯的
Turns out it belonged to the actual Steve Jobs.
什么  真的吗
What? Seriously?
对  女佣不小心拿来的
Yeah, the maid brought it in accidentally
现在他们家想要回去
and the family wants it back.
是吗
Oh, really?
那小索我最好穿上雨鞋
Well, then Li'l So-So better get her galoshes
因为老乔家要大出血咯
'cause that family's about to make it rain!
莉莉  我老板很喜欢那衣服
Lily, listen, my boss is in love with it
也真的给了他鼓励
and he was in a really bad place.
所以对不起  但多少钱都不能
So I'm sorry, but no amount of money
让我把衣服要回来
could make me take it away from him.
两万五怎么样
How about $25,000?
我们一小时内送去给你
We'll have it for you within the hour.
好  我用这件假高领衫
Okay, I'm gonna swap out the mock turtleneck
把那件高领衫换过来
for this mock-mock turtleneck, all right?
你在楼下放哨
You stay down here
确保乔什不从办公室出来  好吗
and make sure Josh doesn't come out of his office, okay?
也确保他别上楼
And make sure he doesn't come upstairs.
真是的  姑娘
Girl, please.
当我索美女三岁小孩吗
You think Li'l So-So was born yesterday?
游戏规则可是我...
The game don't run me, I run the...
-索菲亚  -乔什
- Hey, Sof! - Josh!
高领衫  乔什  高领衫
Turtleneck! Josh turtleneck!
这不是一般的高领衫
Not just any turtleneck.
是我的幸运高领衫
This is my lucky turtleneck.
加比送给我以后
Gabi got this for me and bam!
我应用的下载量飙升
My app sales have skyrocketed.
这衣服真的灵
This shirt is a winner.
乔什
Josh!
你穿着我送的高领衫啊
You're wearing the turtleneck that I got you.
怪不得你卧室里没有
That's why it's not in your bedroom...
我猜的
I would imagine.
这衣服改变了我的人生
This shirt has changed my life.
听到没  加比
Hear that, Gabi?
是不是很棒
Isn't that fantastic?
我再也不脱了
I'm never taking it off.
不脱了
Never!
不脱了吗
Never?
乔什  那你...
I mean Josh, what about--
你睡觉怎么办
what about when you go to sleep?
不脱
No.
那...那万圣节呢
Well, what about-- what about on Halloween?
-我就扮成乔布斯  -可恶
- I'll go as Steve Jobs. - Dammit.
那你骑自行车呢
Well, what about when you go on a bike ride?
加比  骑车的时候我当然会脱掉
Gabi, of course I'm going to take it off if I go on a bike ride.
我不会把让沾上汗的
I'm not going to get it sweaty.
你看起来好紧张
You know, you're all wound up.
我觉得你该去骑车放松下
I think you need to go on a bike ride.
索菲亚  他好紧张
Uh-huh. Sofia, he's tight.
摸摸看  肌肉都僵了
Feel him. He's very tight.
是僵了
Ooh, he is tight.
两位  今天是发布日
Guys, today is my launch day.
我只想坐在电脑前
All I want to do is sit at my computer
穿着我的幸运高领衫
and see how many people download my app
看会有多少人下载应用
while wearing my lucky magic turtleneck.
看来有人挺喜欢加比送的礼物
Looks like someone loves the gift Gabi got them.
不像我的摇头娃娃
Unlike my bobblehead,
我在你办公室没看见呢
which I didn't see in your office.
这个嘛...
Oh, well...
因为我把它移走了
that's 'cause I moved it.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
我还怕你不喜欢它
You know, I was scared that you didn't like it.
我前夫科尔曼有次扔掉了我送的礼物
My ex Coleman once threw out a gift that I gave him and I...
我崩溃了
I was crushed.
到现在都记得
I remember it to this day.
尤兰达
Oh. Yolanda...
我不会扔掉你礼物的
I'd never throw your gift away.
那就好
Good.
所以它在哪
So, where is it?
我交给快递员
Um... I had a messenger pick it up
把它送去市中心的公司办公室了
and they took it to my corporate office downtown
好让大家都看看
so all the people there could see it.
我真是受宠若惊
Oh, I am so flattered!
看到大家都喜欢我也很高兴
You know, I would love to see the people enjoying it.
不如我们现在去你公司的办公室吧
How 'bout we go to your corporate office right now?
我也想去  但我...
You know, I'd love to but I'm...
-正要去骑车  -正要去骑车
- Going on a bike ride. - going on a bike ride.
乔什  你喊我来这里干什么
Josh, why did you want me to meet you in here?
明白了  等我也脱掉
Oh, I see. Let me catch up.
别闹
Knock it off!
埃兰能接受的  他同意我跟你睡
It's cool with Alan, you're one of my free passes.
艾略特  别闹
Elliot! No.
我需要你把尤兰达的礼物找回来
Look, I need you to get Yolanda's gift back.
从垃圾桶里
From the trash.
你把她的礼物扔了吗
You threw her gift away?
不得不扔  吓死我了
I had to! That thing was freaking me out.
谁管为什么  反正你更喜欢我的
Who cares why? You like mine better!
你能帮我吗  艾略特
Are you going to help me, Elliot?
当然
Absolutely.
我帮你踩着脚踏板
I'll push on the little pedal-y thing
你自己伸手拿吧
and you'll reach in and grab it.
不是这个垃圾桶
No, not this trash.
我把它扔进大楼的垃圾道了
I threw it down the building's trash chute.
我才不会去那里
No. I'm not going down there.
我给你一千块
I'll give you a thousand dollars.
不  我还是不去
No, I'm still not going down there.
两千块
$2,000.
你出的钱越多  这事越好笑
The higher the amount, the funnier it gets.
好吧  你婚礼费用我包了
Fine. I'll pay for your wedding.
在夏威夷的游艇上办婚礼
My Hawaiian wedding on a yacht
还请席琳·迪翁来唱《泰坦尼克号》主题曲吗
with Celine Dion singing the love song from "Titanic?"
没问题
Done!
我是这世界的女王
I'm the queen of the world!
好了各位  待会见
All right guys, see you in a bit.
你腰上系着高领衫
Is the bike ride really a good idea
再去骑单车  真的好吗
with the turtleneck wrapped around your waist?
没错  乔什
Uh... she's right, Josh.
万一卷进车轮里  或者被风刮走了呢
You know, it could get caught in a spoke or blow in the wind.
没错  毕竟这里是风城嘛
Yeah, yeah. You know, it is the windy city, after all.
那是芝加哥
That's Chicago.
不过你们说的对
But you guys might be right.
我可不想衣服出什么意外
I don't want anything to happen to it.
给  视线不许离开它
Here. Don't take your eyes off it.
不会的
I won't.
你猜怎么着  不行
You know what? I can't do it.
把高领衫还我
I need my turtleneck back.
好吧
Oh, okay.
把它系在脖子上
Tie it around my neck.
就像披风一样
Like a cape.
没想到吧  加比
Didn't think of that one, did you Gabi?
没有  乔什  你真是把高领衫穿得更帅了
Nope Josh. You've found a way to make turtlenecks even cooler.
对
Yes.
没错
Yes I did.
我们成功了  偷梁换柱
We did it! The 'ol switcheroo.
现在我们只要等他进了电梯
Now all we got to do is wait for him to get in the elevator.
两万五千块一次
$25,000 one...
两万五千块两次
$25,000 two...
两万五千块第三次
$25,000 three...
两万五千块
$25,000
两万五...  乔什
$25-- Josh!
没有自行车
Can't go on a bike ride...
怎么能骑车
...without my bike.
没错  先生
No sir, you cannot.
去拿自行车吧
You go get that bike.
天啊  好险
Oh my god, that was so close.
好  我们快去莉莉店里
Okay, let's hurry. Let's get to Lily's.
衣服呢
Where's the shirt?
不要啊
Nooo!
好了  我再说最后一次
Okay, I'm just going to say this one more time.
这真是你干过最蠢的事
This is the dumbest thing you've ever done.
谁更蠢呢  是蠢蛋
Okay, who's dumber? The dummy?
还是把衣服扔进垃圾桶的蠢蛋
Or the dummy that threw the shirt to the dummy?
行了  我们找到衣服  赶快走
Okay. Let's just get it and get out of here.
好
Okay.
你去拿
Go get it!
我吗
Me?
好吧  我们一起去
Fine, we'll both go.
你都还没进垃圾桶呢  小公主
Okay, we're not even in there yet, princess.
如果里面有老鼠怎么办
What if there's a rat in here?
你们两个在这干什么
What are you two doing here?
乔什也让你们来找摇头娃娃吗
Did Josh send you to look for the bobblehead?
真不巧  它是我的
Well too bad, it's mine!
我们不是找摇头娃娃  是在找...
We're not looking for a bobblehead. We're looking for--
什么  我身上有东西吗
What? What? Is there something on me?
对
Yes!
在哪  在哪
Where? Where is it? Where is it?
在你头上
On your head...
艾略特找到了
Oh, Elliot found it!
艾略特  谢谢你找回了娃娃
Elliot, thank you for finding the bobblehead.
现在请你把它送去我市中心的办公室
Okay, now I need you to take it to my downtown office
明天尤兰达好能...
so tomorrow when Yolanda goes...
什么叫你没找到
what do you mean you didn't find it?
我才把它放进碗橱里
I just put it in the cupboard.
我再打给你
I'll call you back.
好  深呼吸
Okay, breathe.
一个摇头娃娃而已
It's a bobblehead.
一切都有合理解释
Logical explanation for all of this.
我吓到你了吗  小宝贝
Did I scare you, baby?
抱歉  我刚才在倒垃圾
Sorry, I was just taking out the trash.
知道吗  就是扔掉不想要的东西
You know, the place where you throw things out you don't want,
比如蛋壳  脏纸巾  真心的礼物
like eggshells, dirty paper towels, heartfelt gifts...
就像是特意定制的摇头娃娃
like a one of a kind made-to-order bobblehead?
-你都知道了  -没错
- So you know? - Yes, I know.
我在垃圾堆里找到了
I found it in the trash.
是你找到的  谢天谢地
Oh, you found it. Thank god.
所以也是你把它拿走的吗
So you were the one moving it around?
当然了
'course I was.
你不会以为是它自己走的吧
You don't think it walked over there by itself, did you?
怎么会
No.
那说话声音也是你吗
And-- and you were the one doing the voice?
-什么声音  -没事
- No. What voice? - Nothing!
尤兰达  我知道不该扔掉它
Yolanda, I know I shouldn't have thrown it away
但应用发布要逼疯我了
but my launch day was making me crazy
还看着我自己摇头晃脑地笑自己
and staring at my own head just bobbling around judging me,
是我反应过度了
I overreacted.
我能理解  乔什
I guess I understand, Josh.
看起来是有点诡异
I mean, it it is a little creepy looking.
那个娃娃  不是你脑袋
The doll, not your head.
你脑袋很好看
Nice head.
说真的  我很内疚
Seriously, I felt so bad.
现在已经派艾略特去垃圾箱找了
I have Elliot in the dumpster right now looking for it.
我让他出来
Gonna tell him to get out.
你真的想补偿我吗
You really want to make this up to me?
我知道我想
You know I do.
那就等下再打
Hold off on that phone call.
快  艾略特  把衣服给我们
Come on, Elliot. Just give us the shirt.
想得美
I would, except no.
这里面有蹊跷[闻起来奇怪]  不光是钻进
Something smells funny, and it's not just the wood shavings
我鞋子里的仓鼠笼木渣
from that hamster cage that's filling my loafer.
为什么两个女孩会爬进垃圾桶
Why would two girls crawl through filth
找一件丑死人的涤纶衣服
for an ugly polyblend shirt?
没错  这根本不值钱
Exactly. It's just a worthless shirt.
那你们也不会介意我用衣服
Oh, so then you won't mind if I use this shirt
擦一下这滩
to wipe up this unidentified sludge
最好是酸奶的白色不明物咯
that you better hope to god is greek yogurt.
不要
No!
艾略特  我们为什么想要这衣服不重要
Elliot, it doesn't matter why we want the shirt.
好吗  给我们就好
Okay? Just give it to us!
那就这样办
Here's how this is gonna go down.
你们找到摇头娃娃
You find my bobblehead,
我就把这丑衣服给你们
I give you this hideous shirt
大家皆大欢喜地出去
and we all walk out of here winners.
黄师傅家的外卖吗
Pro Wong's take out?
我们家的垃圾扔完了
Well, that's the end of our trash,
不过还有芬克小姐
But here's a little something
和她十二只猫向你问好哦
compliments of Miss Finkel and her twelve cats.
艾略特  这里没有
Elliot, it's not here!
继续找
Keep looking.
每个成人尿布都要翻过来看
Leave no adult diaper unturned.
不要
No... no!
够了
Stop it! Stop!
我想到了另一个办法
I just thought of another way to do this.
抓住他
Get him!
尤兰达
Yolanda!
你说得对  这样不礼貌
You're right. That is rude.
艾略特喝咖啡喜欢加奶
Elliot likes cream with his coffee.
我觉得行了
I think he's had enough.
给他点甜头[骨头]吧
Throw him a bone.
我可不只给他根骨头  我扔了一整只鸡
I did better than that. I threw a whole chicken!
好吧
All right.
明明二对一
It's two against one!
你怎么这么有劲
How are you so strong?
你们知道我去过多少次巴尼商场的
Do you know how many Barney's Warehouse Sales
大清仓吗  贱人
I've been to, bitches?
有情况
Incoming!
不
No!
天啊  是摇头娃娃
Oh my god! It's the bobblehead!
衣服给你们  贱人
Here's your shirt, bitches!
我已经洗两次澡了
I just took a second shower
闻起来还是一股酸辣汤味
and I still smell like hot and sour soup.
三次就好了
Third one's the charm.
才不会
No, it's not.
我们差一点就有钱了
We were so close to being rich.
我知道  我都想好怎么花那钱了
I know. I had big plans for that money.
我可以躺在卡波的沙滩上
I was going to pay off my student loans...
还清我的学生贷款
...while lying on a beach in Cabo.
是啊  我们去不成卡波了
Yeah, well we're not going to Cabo.
想知道为什么吗
You want to know why?
因为你直觉糟透了吗
Because you have terrible, terrible instincts?
不  因为我们太贪婪
No, because we were greedy.
我们就不该把乔什的衣服拿走
We never should have taken that shirt back from Josh.
我们现在说好
Let's make a pact right now
再也不让贪婪控制自己
to never let ourselves be controlled by greed.
没问题
Done.
姑娘们  衣服呢
Hey ladies, where's the shirt?
被撕坏了
Well, it's torn.
贪婪把它撕成了两半
Greed ripped it in half.
我要把你们撕成两半
I'm gonna rip you both in half,
衣服给我
Give me that shirt.
等等  这不是我卖你们的那件
Wait a minute, this isn't the shirt I sold you.
什么
What?
你觉得乔布斯会穿女式M号吗
You think Steve Jobs wore a woman's medium?
什么  天啊
What? Oh my god. Oh my god.
那说明艾略特头上的不是这件衣服
That means Elliot must have had a different shirt on his head.
说明真的衣服还在...
That means the real shirt is still in the...
我能去卡波了
I'm going to Cabo!
这还能卖几个钱
Eh, I could get a couple of bucks for this.
乔什  该洗衣服了
Hey Josh, it's laundry day.
暗示你一下
Hint hint.
我说暗示  意思是赶快把那臭衣服脱下来
And by hint hint, I mean take off the damn shirt because you stink.
抱歉  尤兰达  我不脱
Sorry, Yolanda. Not taking it off.
我的应用这周下载量都很惊人
My app has been crushing it all week.
请脱了吧
Please?
我九十分钟以后就还你
I mean, I'll have it back to you in 90 minutes.
抱歉  我不冒这个险
Sorry, I'm not taking that risk.
现在麻烦告诉加比  我可以吃午餐了
Now please tell Gabi I'm ready for my lunch.
好吧
Okay.
太棒了
Yes!
或许是该换了
Maybe she's right.
加比
Gabi?
乔什要吃午餐了
Josh's ready for his lunch.
好  稍等
Yeah, wait a sec!